[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which terms means an irrational fear of the sea or the ocean?", "correct_answer": "Thalassophobia", "incorrect_answers": ["Somniphobia", "Selachophobia", "None of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Are there any complete dodo skeletons anywhere in the world?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This part of the worlds population is on a vegetarian diet.", "correct_answer": "1/4", "incorrect_answers": ["1/20", "1/2", "1/10"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If a wireless network is set up in a home, yet the signal is weak in certain areas, you may buy one of these to increase the existing signal strength.", "correct_answer": "Repeater", "incorrect_answers": ["Modem", "Router", "Satellite Dish"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The original Batman swore an oath to himself never to kill another human-an oath he has attempted to hold true to, ever since.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is a formicary?", "correct_answer": "A nest of ants", "incorrect_answers": ["The place where scorpions live", "A list of prescribable medicines", "A device to mix chemicals"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What 1960 movie, directed by John Sturges, is an American remake of the Japanese movie  Shichinin no samurai?", "correct_answer": "The Magnificent Seven", "incorrect_answers": ["The Dirty Dozen", "The Wild Bunch", "The Great Escape"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This person wrote what historians recognize as the worlds first computer program -- a method for calculating Bernoulli numbers with Charles Babbages analytical engine.", "correct_answer": "Lord Byrons daughter", "incorrect_answers": ["Johnny von Neumann", "Benjamin Bannekker", "Blaise Pascal"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Einsteins father owned a company that made small magnetos, which he was later forced to sell to this, much larger corporation.", "correct_answer": "Siemens", "incorrect_answers": ["Bavarian Electrical Supplies , GmbH", "Krups", "BMW"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is the founder of the clothing brand Lacoste?", "correct_answer": "Ren\u00e9 Lacoste", "incorrect_answers": ["Pierre Lacoste", "Johnathon P. Lacoste", "Marc L. M. Smith"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who portrays Nicoles (Staci Keanan) two fathers on the TV sitcom My Two Dads?", "correct_answer": "Paul Reiser and Greg Evigan", "incorrect_answers": ["Tony Randall and Jack Klugman", "Walter Matthau and Art Carney", "Matthew Broderick and Nathan Lane"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The atomic number of the chemical element Tin is 50.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]